A Guide to the University of Virginia Student Council General Records, 1972-1975
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Student Council General Records 1972-1975
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-23/2/4.774
This collection consists of ca. 3000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library by the Student Council, 4th Floor South Newcomb Hall on 1977 June 29.
Scope and Content Information
General records of student council, including correspondence, memoranda, clippings and related papers concerning a wide variety of council projects and activities arranged alphabetically by subject.
Contents List
- Academics Committee (Box 1)
- Adderesses (Box 1)
- Administrative Committees (Box 1)
- Agenda for Student (Box 1)
- Allocation Lists, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Alumni Association (Box 1)
- Ampitheatre (Box 1)
- Annual Report (Box 1)
- Appointments - Dean of Faculty (Box 1)
- Appointments/Search Committees (Box 1)
- Appropriations Committees (Box 1)
- Appropriations Committees (Box 1)
- ARC (Box 1)
- Athletic Admissions (Box 1)
- Athletics (Box 1)
- Barbour, Mayor Charles (Box 1)
- Board of Visitors - Past Correspondence and Records (Box 1)
- Briefing Materials (Box 1)
- Buckley Amendment (Box 1)
- Budget - Student Council (Box 1)
- By-Laws (Box 1)
- Calendar and Scheduling Committee (Box 2)
- Career Planning and Placement (Box 2)
- Catalyst, The (Box 2)
- Cavalier Daily (Box 2)
- City/County (Box 2)
- Club Sports (Box 2)
- Committee Appointments (Box 2)
- Committee Structure (Box 2)
- Committees (Box 2)
- Commonwealth Day (Box 2)
- Community in the Academical Village (Box 2)
- Community Relations (Box 2)
- Comprehensive Fee, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Correspondence re Allocations (Box 2)
- Correspondence re Constitution (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General - Dan Hobbs (Box 2)
- Correspondence, General - Larry Sabato (Box 2)
- Correspondence re Student Council (Box 2)
- Correspondence re Student Legal Services (Box 2)
- Crime - "A Study of Criminal Victimization on a University Campus and in the Surrounding Community" directed by James W. Fox, 1976 (Box 2)
- Curriculum Evaluation (Box 2)
- Reginald Dance Case (Jurisdictional Problems) (Box 2)
- Dormitory Health Aide Program (Box 2)
- Double Tax Bill (Box 2)
- Easter's Weekend (Box 2)
- Elections Committee (Box 2)
- Equal Opportunity Counselor Program (Box 3)
- Equal Opportunity Programs (Box 3)
- Equal Rights Amendment (Box 3)
- Expenditure Receipts for Honor Committee Election (Box 3)
- Expenditures for Honor Referendum - Journals (Box 3)
- Expenditures for Student Council and Judiciary, April 1976 (Box 3)
- Extern Program (Box 3)
- Fall 73 Appearls (Box 3)
- Fall Packet (Box 3)
- Fall 72 - Restoration of Graduated Tax (Box 3)
- FEI Conference (Box 3)
- First Year Council, 1973-1975, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Founder's Day (Box 3)
- Future of the University Committee (Box 4)
- Future of the University Committee, 3 folders (Box 4)
- Graves Mt. Lodge, 1975 (Box 4)
- Graves Mountain Meeting, 1974 (Box 4)
- Guidelines for Student Organizations (Box 4)
- Hearing Packet (Box 4)
- Higher Education Commission (Box 4)
- Honor Committee (Box 4)
- Housing (Box 4)
- Housing Migration Study (Box 4)
- Inauguration Committee (Box 4)
- Institutional Self-Study Steering Committee (Box 4)
- Insurance Forum (Box 4)
- Leadership in Action - Larry Sabato; Dan Hobbs; Jamey Bryan; Martha Yeitz; Paul Freeman; Ann Sowder (Box 4)
- Long Distance Telephone Calls (Box 5)
- McCormick Road Gates (Box 5)
- Mail-out to all students - Sabato and Hobbs (Box 5)
- Members - Student Council, 4 folders (Box 5)
- Miscellaneous (Box 5)
- Mobile Home Act (Box 5)
- Mobile Homes (Box 5)
- Model Budget (Box 5)
- Mountain Lake - 1969 (Box 5)
- National Student Lobby (Box 5)
- Noise Ordinance (Box 5)
- Off-Ground Housing (Box 6)
- Officers - Summer Residence (Box 6)
- Officer Space Applications (Box 6)
- Ombudsman Service (Box 6)
- Open Seat Applications - Student Council (Box 6)
- Past President's Annual Report (Box 6)
- President's Reports (Box 6)
- Picture Files - U. Va. Police (Box 6)
- Presidential Selection Process (Box 6)
- Priority Guidelines (Box 6)
- Professors Salaries (Box 6)
- Proposed Centel Pay Phone Rate Hike (Box 6)
- Provost Nominations (Box 6)
- Publications Committee (Box 6)
- Publicity for Office of Career Planning & Placement (Box 6)
- Public Occasions - Founder's Day (Box 6)
- Radioactive Waste (Box 6)
- Rape and Assault (Box 7)
- Recognized Organizations (Box 7)
- Recruitment - High School (Box 7)
- Registration - 1974 (Box 7)
- Research Papers - Legislation and Correpsondence (Box 7)
- Revision of Model Budget, Spring 1974 (Box 7)
- Sabato's, Larry - Annual Report (Box 7)
- SAF Poll, 1973 (Box 7)
- SAF Referendum, 1973 (Box 7)
- Sample Packets to Council Members - Hobbs, Sabato (Box 7)
- Scholarships (Box 7)
- Shockley Debate (Box 8)
- Social Development Commission (Box 8)
- Spring 73 Appeals (Box 8)
- Spring 73 Hearings (Box 8)
- Staff Housing (Box 8)
- State Council of Higher Education (Box 8)
- State Finances (Box 8)
- Statements of Rule Understanding for Honor Committee Elections, Jan 24, 1976 (Box 8)
- Statements of Rule Understanding for Student Council and Judiciary, Spring, 1976 (Box 8)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee (Box 8)
- Student's Attorney - Resume (Box 8)
- Student Health (Box 8)
- Student Health Committee (Box 8)
- Summer Session (Box 8)
- Supersounds (Box 8)
- Tenure (Box 8)
- Transfer Students Program (Box 8)
- Undergraduate Reader's Library (Box 8)
- Undergraduate Reader's Library, 2 folders (Box 9)
- United Way Campaign (Box 9)
- University Committees (Box 9)
- University - Community Open Forum (Box 9)
- University Police (Box 9)
- University Tuesday (Box 9)
- University Union (Box 9)
- Use of University Facilities (Box 9)
- Virginia Housing Study Commission (Box 9)
- Voter Information (Box 9)
- Voter Participation (Students) (Box 9)